<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on R4All</title>
    <link>/R4All_website/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on R4All</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/R4All_website/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Datasets</title>
      <link>/R4All_website/books/datasets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/R4All_website/books/datasets/</guid>
      <description>Datasets used in Getting Started with R, Second Edition All the datasets (and more) one zip file.
We don&amp;rsquo;t any longer distribute datasets for the first edition of Getting Started with R.
Insights from Data Coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with R, First Edition</title>
      <link>/R4All_website/books/gswr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/R4All_website/books/gswr1/</guid>
      <description>“Blowing away any feeling of intimidation is what this book is about.” – Graeme Ruxton, Trends in Ecology Evolution.
Designed for undergraduates, grad students and staff, we show you how to import, explore, graph, and start analysing your data, keeping you focused on your ultimate goals.
 A simple, easy, and engaging introduction to R for biologists. Walks readers through the fundamentals of using R, from that first step of importing datathrough to managing and exploring it and ultimately producing figures and analyses Delivers an efficient, accurate, reliable, and reproducible workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with R, Second Edition</title>
      <link>/R4All_website/books/gswr2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/R4All_website/books/gswr2/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce the second edition of Getting Started with R Paperback at OUP, Amazon UK, Amazon.com, Amazon.de, Buch.ch
Electric version at Oxford Scholarship Online.
We got great feedback about our book &amp;ldquo;Getting Started with R, An Introduction for Biologists&amp;rdquo;, but realised over the last couple of years that we were using and teaching R very differently from what we wrote about back in 2010. So we have almost completely rewritten for a very different and new Second Edition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights from Data</title>
      <link>/R4All_website/books/insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/R4All_website/books/insights/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>